export const flashcards = [
  { front: "こんにちは", frontSub: "Konnichiwa", back: "Halo / Selamat siang" },
  { front: "ありがとう", frontSub: "Arigatou", back: "Terima kasih" },
  { front: "さようなら", frontSub: "Sayounara", back: "Selamat tinggal" },
  { front: "すみません", frontSub: "Sumimasen", back: "Maaf / Permisi" },
  { front: "はい", frontSub: "Hai", back: "Ya" },
  { front: "いいえ", frontSub: "Iie", back: "Tidak" },
  { front: "日本", frontSub: "Nihon", back: "Jepang" },
  { front: "わたし", frontSub: "私", back: "Saya" },
  { front: "猫", frontSub: "Neko", back: "Kucing" },
  { front: "犬", frontSub: "Inu", back: "Anjing" },
];
